Guide to the Records of the American Institute of the City of New York for the Encouragement of Science and Invention 1808-1983 (bulk, 1828-1940) MS 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Annual Fair Years, 1808-1930
  - Subseries 3: Bound Volumes, 1828-1936, n.d.
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 44th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1875 (Offsite-box 612, Volume 232)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 45th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1876 (Offsite-box 612, Volume 233)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 46th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1877 (Offsite-box 613, Volume 234)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 47th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1878 (Offsite-box 613, Volume 235)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 48th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1879 (Offsite-box 613, Volume 236)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 49th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1880 (Offsite-box 613, Volume 237)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 50th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1881 (Offsite-box 613, Volume 238)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 51st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1882 (Offsite-box 614, Volume 239)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 52nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1883 (Offsite-box 614, Volume 240)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 53rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1884 (Offsite-box 614, Volume 241)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 54th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1885 (Offsite-box 614, Volume 242)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 55th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1886 (Offsite-box 614, Volume 243)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 56th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1887 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 244)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 57th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1888 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 245)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 58th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1889 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 246)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 59th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1890 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 247)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 60th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1891 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 248)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 61st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1892 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 249)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 65th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1896 (Volume 250)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 66th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1897 (Volume 251)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 67th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1898 (Volume 252)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 68th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1899 (Volume 253)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 69th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1900 (Volume 254)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 71st Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger), 1902 (Volume 255)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 72nd Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1903 (Volume 256)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 73rd Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1904 (Volume 257)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 74th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1905 (Volume 258)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 75th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1906 (Volume 259)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 76th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1907 (Volume 260)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 77th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1908 (Volume 261)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 78th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1909 (Volume 262)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 79th Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1910 (Volume 263)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 83rd Annual Fair of the American Institute (In hollinger, unbound material), 1914 (Volume 264)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Collections, 1859-1875 (Offsite-box 639, Volume 267)
    - [Receipt books] C. P. Dickinson, 3rd Avenue Entrance -- Receipts for Tickets -- 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1869 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 268)
    - [Receipt books] A. C. Wing, 63rd Street Entrance -- Receipts for Tickets -- 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1869 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 269)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Tickets -- 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1869 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 270)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Entry Fees, 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1869 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 271)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Entry Fees, 39th Annual Fair of the American Institute (1 of 2), 1870 June-September (Offsite-box 627, Volume 272A)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Entry Fees, 39th Annual Fair of the American Institute (2 of 2), 1870 September-October (Offsite-box 627, Volume 272B)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Collections, 1875-1885 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 273)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Entry Fees, 65th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1896 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 274)
    - [Receipt books] Description of Models, Machines, etc. at the Repository of the American Institute, [1839] (Offsite-box 633, Volume 275)
    - [Receipt books] Published Library Catalogue with Annotations, [1852] (Offsite-box 635, Volume 276)
    - [Receipt books] Receipts for Books taken from the Library of the American Institute, 1845-1850 (Offsite-box 633, Volume 277)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1851 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 278)
    - [Receipt books] Donations, American Institute Library, 1851-1870 (Offsite-box 633, Volume 279)
    - [Receipt books] Name Index to Record of Issue of Books 1851-1872 (Offsite-box 634, Volume 280)
    - [Receipt books] Record of Issue of Books ("Ledger A" on spine; names of borrowers in separate volume), 1851-1872 (Offsite-box 634, Volume 281)
    - [Receipt books] Published Library Catalogue with Annotations, 1852 (Offsite-box 635, Volume 282)
    - [Receipt books] Published Library Catalogue with Annotations, 1852 (Offsite-box 635, Volume 283)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1852 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 284)
    - [Receipt books] Members of the American Institute Notified of their Indebtedness, 1854 (Offsite-box 630, Volume 285)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1855 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 286)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1856 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 287)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1857 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 288)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1858 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 289)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1859 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 290)
    - [Receipt books] Inventory -- American Institute, 1860 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 291)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1860 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 292)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1862 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 293)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1863 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 294)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1865 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 295)
    - [Receipt books] Contracts with Transportation Companies to Return all Exhibits Free Freight, 1867-1875 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 296)
    - [Receipt books] Record of Issue of Books, 1870-1878 (Offsite-box 635, Volume 297)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1872 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 298)
    - [Receipt books] Record of Issue of Books, 1872-1888 (Offsite-box 634, Volume 299)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1873 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 300)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1876 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 301)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1878 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 302)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1889 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 303)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1890 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 304)
    - [Receipt books] Engraving; Cups, Medals, etc. (in Hollinger box), 1892 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 305)
    - [Receipt books] "Regimental Order Book" [Catalogue of Library Serials and Pamphlets], ca. 1890 (Offsite-box 634, Volume 306)
    - [Receipt books] Address Book, ca. 1915 (Offsite-box 630, Volume 307)
    - [Receipt books] Numerical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute (Partial), n.d. (Offsite-box 635, Volume 308)
    - [Receipt books] Numerical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute, n.d. (Offsite-box 635, Volume 309)
    - [Receipt books] Published Library Catalogue, n.d. (Offsite-box 635, Volume 310)
    - [Receipt books] "Memorandums; Insurance A/C of U. S. Bonds and Contents of Document Boxes and Dark Closet" (Offsite-box 635, Volume 311)
    - [Receipt books] Numerical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute #'s 14027-15121, n.d. (Offsite-box 641, Volume 312)
    - [Receipt books] Numerical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute #'s 1-14026, n.d. (Offsite-box 640, Volume 313)
    - [Receipt books] Supplementary Analytical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute, n.d. (Offsite-box 639, Volume 314)
    - [Receipt books] Supplementary Alphabetical Catalogue of the Library of the American Institute, n.d. (Offsite-box 639, Volume 315)
    - [Receipt books] Address Book -- Photographical Section, n.d. (Offsite-box 630, Volume 316)
    - [Receipt books] Employees Tickets, n.d. (Offsite-box 459, Volume 317)
    - [Receipt books] Suggestion Book, American Institute Library, n.d. (Offsite-box 639, Volume 318)
    - [Registers] Admission Fees and Annual Dues, No. 1, 1828-1849 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 319)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 3rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1831 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 320)
    - [Registers] Admission Fees and Annual Dues, No. 2, 1831-1844 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 321)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 7th to 17th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1834-1844 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 322)
    - [Registers] Library Permits, 1834-1845 (Offsite-box 636, Volume 323)
    - [Registers] 1) Invitations -- 10th Annual Fair of the American Institute 2) Diplomas Awarded -- 11th Annual fair of the American Institute, 1837-1838 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 324)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 15th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1842 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 325)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 15th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1842 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 326)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 327)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Volume 328)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1843 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 329)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 330)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 331)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 332)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 333)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- [Agricultural and Horticultural Dept.], 1844 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 334)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 335)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 336)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1845 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 337)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1845 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 338)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Manufacturing and Mechanical Dept., 1845 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 339)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 340)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 341)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 342)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 18th to 22nd Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1845-1849 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 343)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Fine Arts, 1846 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 344)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Manufacturing and Mechanical Dept., 1846 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 345)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1846 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 346)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1846 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 347)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1846 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 348)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1846 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 349)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1846 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 350)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1846 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 351)
    - [Registers] Transactions of the American Institute [Subscription Book], 1846-1871 (Offsite-box 635, Volume 352)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1847 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 353)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Manufacturing and Mechanical Dept., 1847 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 354)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1847 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 355)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1847 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 356)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1848 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 357)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1848 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 358)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical Dept., 1848 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 359)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical Dept., 1848 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 360)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1848 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 361)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute (1 of 2), 1848 (Offsite-box 627, Volume 362A)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute (2 of 2), 1848 (Offsite-box 627, Volume 362B)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1848 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 363)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1849 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 364)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept., 1849 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 365)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1849 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 366)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1849 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 367)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1849 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 368)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1849 (Offsite-box 618, Volume 369)
    - [Registers] Invitations -- 22nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1849 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 370)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1850 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 371)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1850 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 372)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept., 1850 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 373)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1850 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 374)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1850 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 375)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept., 1850 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 376)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 23rd to 30th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1850-1858 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 377)
    - [Registers] Admission Fees and Annual Dues, No. 3, 1850-1865 (Offsite-box 630, Volume 378)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1851 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 379)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1851 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 380)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1851 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 381)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mathematical and Philosophical Instruments., 1851 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 382)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1851 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 383)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1851 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 384)
    - [Registers] Visitors' Register, 1851-1888 (Offsite-box 636, Volume 385)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1852 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 386)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1852 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 387)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept., 1852 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 388)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1852 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 389)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute --Cattle, 1852 (Volume 390)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1852 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 391)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 26th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1853 (Volume 392)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 26th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept., 1853 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 393)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 26th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1853 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 394)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 26th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1853 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 570)
      The register's pages have a pre-printed title, but there are no entries.
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1853 (Offsite-box 617, Volume 395)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1855 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 396)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1855 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 397)
    - [Registers] Judges -- 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 398)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 28th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Cattle, 1856 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 399)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 28th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1856 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 400)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 28th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1856 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 401)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 28th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1856 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 402)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1857 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 403)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- [Mechanical and Manufacturing Dept.], 1857 (Offsite-box 619, Volume 404)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Alphabetical List, 1857 (Offsite-box 620, Volume 405)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1857 (Offsite-box 620, Volume 406)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1857 (Offsite-box 620, Volume 407)
    - [Registers] Register of Entries in the 30th Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1858 (Offsite-box 620, Volume 408)
    - [Registers] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 31st to 56th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1859-1887 (Offsite-box 620, Volume 409)